Hastings, James F.; Papers apap254
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Hastings, James F. Papers
1956-1976
Undated
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap254
8.68 cubic ft.
This collection documents James F. Hastings' time as a member of the New York State Assembly from the Cattaraugus County district from 1963-1965, a member of the New York State Senate from 1966-1968, and a Representative for New York in the United States House of Representatives from 1969 until his resignation in 1976.
Collection X
Biographical / Historical
James F. Hasting was born in Olean, Cattaraugus County, New York on April 10, 1926. Hasting served in the United States Navy in flight squadrons from 1943 through 1946. After the War, Hasting was a sales representative for Procter and Gamble. In 1952, Hasting began to manage the radio station WHDL, and in 1964 he became the national advertising manager for the Times Herald, and a partner in the real estate and insurance firm of Hastings & Jewell. During this time, Hasting began to get involved in local politics and served as a member of the Allegany (N.Y.) Town Board for ten years, and Allegany police justice for five years.
Hasting, a Republican, was nominated to the New York State Assembly in 1962 and sat as a member until 1965, when he earned a seat in the New York State Senate in 1966. In this position, Hasting was a delegate to the Republican National Convention in 1968. Hasting was also a delegate to the Republican National Convention in 1972, after securing a seat in the United States Congress in 1969. Hasting was in office until 1976, and served in the 91st-94th Congresses.
Hasting resigned on January 20, 1976 to become the President of the Associated Industries Trade Group in Albany, New York. That same year, Hastings was convicted of mail fraud and filming false payroll information. Hasting served 14 months in the United States Penitentiary, Allenwood. After Hasting was released, he moved to Florida. Eventually Hasting moved back to Allegany and he died there on October 24, 2014.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains papers from James F. Hastings' time in the New York State Assembly, New York State Senate, and U.S. House of Representatives. It contains research, legislation, correspondence, and newspaper clippings throughout the years of Hastings' political career. While James F. Hastings sponsored a variety of legislation, there is a focus on background research and bills from his time in the House Subcommittee on Public Health.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into two series – Series 1 is Hastings' time in Congress, and Series 2 is the compilation of his time in the New York State Assembly and New York State Senate. The files are arranged in chronological order.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
James F. Hasting donated his papers to Syracuse University in 1968-1969. Additional materials were donated in 1976. In 2006, all materials were transferred to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Hastings, James F., 1926-2014; Politics and Politicians; New York State-- Assembly; New York State--Senate; Bills (legislative records); Correspondence; Newspaper clippings; United States. Congress. House
- U.S. Congress, 1963-1976; Undated; 1; 6.21 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  - H.R. 14086 Amend Community Mental Health Centers Act, 1963; 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - H.R. 14237 Amend Mental Retardation Act of 1963, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Common Situs Picketing Bill H.R. 100, 1967; 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - H. Concurrent Resolution 145 Route 219, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - H. J. Res. 482 Mid Atlantic States Air Pollution Control Compact, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Rep. James F. Hastings Election Result, 1968; 1970; 1972; 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1969 January; 1970 January (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1969 March; 1970 March (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1969 April; 1970 April (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1969 May; 1970 May; Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1969 June; 1970 June (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1969 July; 1970 July (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1969 August; 1970 August (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1969 September; 1970 September (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1969 October; 1970 October; Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1969 November; 1970 November; Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1969 December; 1970 December (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - H. Concurrent Resolution 196 International Dairy Agreement, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - H. Concurrent Resolution 325 Vietnam - Protest Against Prisoners Held, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - H. Concurrent Resolution 340 Mandatory Extradition of Hijackers, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - H. Concurrent Resolution 357 Comply with Geneva Convention, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - H. Concurrent Resolution 386 Adopt Policies - Housing Industry, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - H. Concurrent Resolution 437 Astronauts Religion, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - H. J. Res. 861 Astronauts Memorial Commission, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - H. J. Res. 895 Create Joint Committee to Study National College Study Congress, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - H. R. 4818 Gun Legislation Strengthen Penalty, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - H. R. 7025 Amend Federal Food, Drug, and Cosmetic Act, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - H. R. 7505 Motor Vehicle Inspection, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - H. R. 7575 Amend Internal Revenue Code of 1954 - Limit Deductions on Farm Income, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - H. R. 7734 Amend Federal Water Pollution Control Act, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - H. R. 8390 1970 Census, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - H. R. 8533 Amend Chapt. 55 of Title 10 of U.S. Code Veterans Dependents, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - H. R. 9428 Capitol Guide Service, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - H. R. 10414 Emergency Telephone No. 911, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - H. R. 10574 Dwight David Eisenhower National Airport, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - H. R. 10821 Suspend Federal Financial Assistance Campus Riots, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - H. R. 10822 Ball and Roller Bearings, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - H. R. 10890 Renewal of Broadcast Licenses, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - H. R. 10962 Apporionment of Population for Congress, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - H. R. 11135 Amend Title 13 - Census - Increase Penalties - Disclosure, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - H. R. 12084 Authorize Study of Essential Railroad Passenger Service, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - H. R. 12426 Amend Public Health Service - National Kidney Disease Act, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - H. R. 12577 Increase Exemption to $1,000, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - H. R. 12749 Minting of Silver Dollars - Eisenhower Likeness, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - H. R. 13311 to Facilitate Movement In Interstate Comm., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - H. R. 13355 Federal Disclosure, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - H. R. 13374 Amend Federal Water Pollution Control Act, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - H. R. 13443 Consent to Connecticut - New York Railroad Passenger Transportation, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - H. R. 13832 Minimum Standards for Railroad Passenger, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - H. R. 13974 Extend Benefits Under U.S. Code to Law Enforcement Officers, and Firemen, Etc., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - H. R. 14090 Amend Title 38 Education Provisions, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - H. R. 14239 Amend Social Security Act - Increase Benefits, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - H. R. 14388 Amend Food Stamp Act of 1964, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - H. R. 14440 International Fair Trade, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - H. R. 14494 Revise Federal Election Laws - Financing, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - H. R. 14646 Connecticut - New York Railroad Passenger, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - H. R. 14733 Amend Public Health Service Act, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - H. R. 14830 Internal Revenue Provide Credit Taxes - Education, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - H. R. 15014 Hi-Jacking Amend Criminal Penalties Generally, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - H. R. 18583 Amend Public Health Service Act Re: Drugs (Research and Prevention of Abuse), 1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - H. Res. 468 Mirv, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - H. Res. 490 Geneva Protocol Ratification Banning Use of Gas, Etc., 1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - H. Res. 567 Concerning Withdrawals From Vietnam, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - H. Res. 648 Resolution Toward Peace, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - H. Res. 701 Investigation of New Mobilization Communication to End War, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - H. Res. 762 Res. to Expedite Gen. Appropriation Measures, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - H. Res. 758 Create Standing Committee on Environment, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - H. R. 7371 Legislation Reorganization Act, 1969; Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - H. R. 7507 Judges Retire Upon Attaining Age 70, 1969; Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - H. R. 13977 Amend Public Health Service Act - National Institute of Marine Medicine, 1969; Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - H. R. 11576 Provide for Annual Reports to Congress by Comptroller, 1969; Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - H. R. 11817 Guidelines to Eliminate Court Pressures for Redistricting, 1969; Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Early Press Releases, 1969; Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - H. J. Res. 1096 National Memorial Week (Judiciary), 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - H. R. 8766 Newspaper Preservation Act, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - H. R. 11102 Amend Provisions of Public Health Service Act, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - H. R. 13195 to Amend Title 10 of U.S. Code Flag to Parents, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - H. R. 13651 Amend U.S. Code to Permit Active Duty to Count for Educational Purposes, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - H. R. 14793 Amend Section 32 of Bankhead - Jones Farm Tenant Act, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - H. R. 14965 Persons Displaced By Federally Assisted Projects, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - H. R. 19318 Public Health Service Family Planning, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - James F. Hastings Legislation, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - H. R. 7506 "Stop and Frisk", 1969-1970; Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - H. R. 11935 Provide Legal Fees for Draftees Seeking Reclassification, 1969-1970; Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - H. R. 13274 Welfare Bill, 1969-1970; Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Insertions In The Record, 1969-1970; Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - H. J. Res. 865 Proposing Amendment - 18 Years Old Vote Federal Election, 1969; 1971 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - James F. Hastings Voting Record - 91st Congress, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - H. R. 13182 Private Bill for Relief of Frank E. Dart, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - H. R. 12194 Federal Revenue Sharing Act, 1969-1971; Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1970 February (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - H. Concurrent Resolution 543 Voluntary Armed Forces Armed Services Committee, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - H. J. Res. 1166 National Volunteer Firemen's Week, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - H. J. Res. 1172 Appointment of Supreme Court Judges, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - H. J. Res. 1219 Representation of D.C. In House of Representatives, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - H. J. Res. 1305 Amendments to the Waterfront Commission and Airport Compact, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - H. R. 15656 Amend Ftc Consumer Class Action Act, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - H. R. 16024 Environmental Quality Government Operations, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - H. R. 16027 Environmental Quality Committee on Public Works, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - H. R. 16030 Environmental Quality Public Works, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - H. R. 16075 Amend Railroad Retirement Act Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - H. R. 16120 to Require Political Campaign Financing Disclosure in D.C. - D.C. Committee, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - H. R. 16178 Economic Tax Credit - W&M, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - H. R. 16359 Interstate and Foreign Commerce Amend Public Health Service Act, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - H. R. 16569 Explosives Transfer Tax Ways and Means Committee, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - H. R. 16847 National College of Ecological and Environmental Studies, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - H. R. 17158 Prohibiting Unsolicited Distribution of Credit Cards, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - H. R. 17277 Benefits, Care, or Assistance for Indian Tribes, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - H. R. 17822 Orderly Trade In Textile Articles, Etc., 1970 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - H. R. 17978 To Limit Sale or Distribution of Mailing Lists, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - H. R. 17981 Enabling Secretary of Agriculture to Develop Resources of National Forests, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - H. R. 18110 Amend Public Health Service Act, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - H. R. 18142 Establish National Catastrophic Illness Program, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - H. R. 18205 Rules Re: Military Hostilities In Absence of Declaration of War, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - H. R. 18487 Amend International Travel Act of 1961, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - H. R. 18568 Support for Health Manpower Needs/Mental and Dental Programs, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - H. R. 18583 Amend Public Health Act for Increased Research Into Drug Abuse and Prevention, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - H. R. 18823 Improved Program to Benefit Producers and Consumers of Dairy Products, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - H. R. 18862 More Efficient Passport Services to U.S. Citizens, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - H. R. 18975 Penalties for Violation of Safety Requirement Prescribe by Interstate Commerce Commission, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - H. R. 19535 Humane Treatment of Animals, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - H. R. 19599 Grants to Medical Schools to Promote Training of Physicians, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - H. R. 19874 "Safe Water Bill", 1970 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - H. Res. 788 Peace In Middle East, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - H. Res. 797 Create Committee Investigate Pornography, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - H. Res. 978 U.S. Involvement in S.E. Asia (Cambodia), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - H. Res. 1122 Securing International Compact Through the United States, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - H. Res. 1284 Prisoner of War Citations, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - H. R. 17255 to Amend The Clean Air Act, 1970; Undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - H. R. 19860 Emergency Health Personnel Act, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Drug Prevention and Control, Information and Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism, 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Cancer Legislation, 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1971 January-1971 February (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1971 February; 1972 January-1972 February; Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1971 March; 1972 March-1972 April (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1971 March-1971 April (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1971 May-1971 June (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1971 July-1971 August (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Photo, 1971 September-1971 October (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1971 November-1971 December (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Health Care: Cost, 1971-1972; 1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Health Care: Delivery, 1971-1973; 1975 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1972 May-1972 June; 1973 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Wgr Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings, 1972 July-1972 August (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1972 September-1972 October (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1972 November-1972 December (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Medical Devices Bill, 1972; 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Revenue Sharing Correspondence, 1972-1974; Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - National Heart, Blood Vessel, Lung, and Blood Act, 1972; 1975 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Rural Health Care, 1972-1975; Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1973 January-1973 February (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1973 March-1973 April (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1973 May-1973 June (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1973 July-1973 August (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1973 September-1973 October (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1973 November-1973 December (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Hew Reorganization Hearings, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Public and Allied Health Personnel Act of 1973 H.R. 9341 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Re-Elect Your Congressman Jim Hastings, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Subcom Correspondence Health Allocations, Fiscal Year 1974, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Hearings on Nat; 1 Health Research Fellowship and Traineeship Act of 1973, H. R. 5640, H. R. 7724, Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - toxic Substances Control Act, 1973; Undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - National Health Insurance Hearings, 1973; 1975 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Health Manpower: Podiatry, 1973; 1975; Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - The Protection of Human Subjects Act, H. R. 10403, H. R. 7724, 1973; 1975; Undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Alaskan Pipeline Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Detailed Weekly Voting Record 93Rd Congress (1 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Detailed Weekly Voting Record 93Rd Congress (2 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Health Services Research, Health Statistics, and Medical Libraries Act of 1973, H.R. 11385, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Hearings: Solid Waste, 1973-1974; Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Professional Standards Review organizations Background (Psro), 1973-1974; Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - The Public Health Act of 1973, H. R. 7274, 1973-1974; Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Public Health Service Amendment, Safe Drinking Water Act of 1973, H. R. 1059, H. R. 13002, 1973-1974; Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Public Health and Environment Subcommittee Health Correspondence Misc. (1 of 2), 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Public Health and Environment Subcommittee Health Correspondence Misc. (2 of 2), 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1974 January (Flat-file 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1974 January-1974 February (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1974 March-1974 April (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1974 May-1974 June (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1974 July-1974 August (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1974 September-1974 October (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1974 November-1974 December (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Safe Drinking Water Act, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Safe Drinking Water Act Report, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Testimony of James F. Hastings Before Interstate Commerce, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Health Manpower Legislation Correspondence (1 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Health Manpower Legislation Correspondence (2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Hmo Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Hearings, Subcommittee on Transportation and Commerce Related to Railroads, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Des Background [Diethylstilbestrol, Estrogens In Beef], 1974-1975; Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Hill Burton Legislation Correspondence, 1974-1975; Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - National Health Insurance Background Material (1 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - National Health Insurance Background Material (2 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1975 January-1975 February (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1975 March-1975 April (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Hearings Before The Subcommittee on Transportation and Commerce of the Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce House of Representatives on Oversight on the Implementation of the Rail Re-Organization Act of 1973, 1975 May (Oversize 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1975 May-1975 June (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Hearings Before The Subcommittee on Transportation and Commerce of The Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce House of Representatives First Session on H.R. 6351 and H.R. 7681, 1975 July (Oversize 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1975 July-1975 August (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1975 September-1975 October (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1975 November-1975 December (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Clinical Laboratories Improvement Act, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Communicable Diseases, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Detailed Weekly Voting Record 1st Session, 94th Congress (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Detailed Weekly Voting Record 1st Session, 94th Congress (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Draft: National Safe Drinking Water Strategy, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Evaluation of The Final System Plan's Financial Analysis, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Fiscal Year 1975 Federal Outlays In Summary, New York, Correspondence (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Fiscal Year 1975 Federal Outlays In Summary, New York, Correspondence (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Health Planning Correspondence, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Legislative Correspondence Budget Committee, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Malpractice Legislative Proposals, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Medical Malpractice Hearing NYC, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - National Health Insurance Correspondence, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Resignation, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Nursing Homes Background, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - office of Technology Assessment, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Rail Services Act of 1975 Report (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Rail Services Planning office: A Report to the Congress, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Rail Services Planning Office Interstate Commerce Commission Report of the office of Public Counsel, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Testimonial Dinner Honoring Congressman James F. Hastings, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - U.S. Department of Transportation 8th Annual Report Fiscal Year 1974, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Conference on Medical Malpractice, 1975; Undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - National Health Policy Correspondence, 1975; Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Correspondence Interstate and for Commerce Communications (1 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Correspondence Interstate and for Commerce Communications (2 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Correspondence Interstate and for Commerce Communications (3 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Medical Malpractice Correspondence (1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Medical Malpractice Correspondence (2 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings Special Election, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Hastings Congress Bumper Stickers, Undated (Flat-file 2)
- New York State Legislature, 1956-1968; Undated; 2; 2.47 cubic ft.
  - Annual Report - Vocational Educational and Extension Board, Nassau County, 1956-1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Achievements in Motor Vehicle Administration in New York State of 1959-1966, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Olean Civil Defense, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, 1963; 1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Olean South Union Street Project, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1964 March (Oversize 1, Folder 7)
  - A.B.C. Liquor (Alcoholic Beverage Control Law), 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Allegany State Park, 1964; 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Technical Vocational Legislation, 1964; 1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Educational Law, 1964-1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Thank You Correspondence, 1964-1965; 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Reapportionment (1 of 2), 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Reapportionment (2 of 2), 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Comparative Analysis of New York State Salaries, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Fourth Interim Report State of New York Temporary Commission on Revision of the Penal Law and Criminal Code, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)